http://www.buzzflash.com/privacy

Donate
Privacy PolicyBuzzFlash LLC respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through its compliance with this policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit our website, and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.Comments on Original ContentBuzzFlash LLC maintains a comment section available to its users. Please remember any information disclosed in these areas becomes publicly available, and therefore you should exercise caution when disclosing personal information. BuzzFlash LLC reserves the right to delete offensive comments at its discretion.Linking to Other SitesBuzzFlash LLC contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of linked websites.
Disclosure of Personal Information
BuzzFlash LLC will not use or disclose your personal information, except (i) as described in this privacy policy, (ii) as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or (iii) to a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, or other sale or transfer of some or all of BuzzFlash LLC's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, dissolution, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by BuzzFlash LLC about our website users is among the assets transferred. In case of disclosure of personal information in the event of a sale or transfer of some or all of BuzzFlash LLC assets, you may direct us not to transfer your personal information at any time by contacting us at the address below or by sending an email to BuzzFlash@BuzzFlash.com. This policy does not protect information you post to any online bulletin board or other public forum within our website.
